After about the fourth song, her bangs look like barcodes and her eyebrows disappear.
The kids in the group are assholes. A lot.
It's not a good idea to start.
Do you remember? Or...who was that? Who was that? Like that.
But I'm sure Yutan heard me.
You found the perfect answer.
What?
That was too much to ask for.
I'm sorry.
I'll go now.
If you were to create the most adorable five-member idol group in history, who would you put in it?
Dreamy theme.
I wanted the three of us to think about this together.
Regardless of the group.
Yes, yes, yes.
And with five members, there has to be a balance, right?
I see.
You have to create a balance between all of them being cute.
That's so hard!
Then, let's make the top five.
We'd look like an amazing staff.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm Nagisa Saito from Equal Love.
I know what you mean.
She's an idol.
Curculious idol.
She recently graduated.
That's for sure!
Song SAP UNITE
I'm Aya. Aya is so cute. In my opinion.
She sings well, and I'd like to include her.
Is Aya strong?
Aya is really good.
Who is your favorite member of Aya?
I like Momona-chan from a group called Takaneko.
Matsumoto Momona-chan?
I worked with her before and I thought she was cute.
She has long black hair that looks great with twin-tails.
She has the face of an idol among idols, and I immediately followed her because I thought she was cute.
I definitely want to include her.
Twintail means "idol"?
It's like an old idol image.
That's exactly what I mean by that twintail.
Mayuyu.
That's an idol.
She was an idol.
Can we have a twintail group? We've become a twintail group.
If they had twintails, they'd have Momochi, for example.
All twintails. It's easy to name a group.
Twintailers! Twintailers that don't move!
I'm thinking of the one in the middle of the tummy.
The center person is Nagisa Nato.
Height is also important, isn't it?
Momochi-san is small in stature, so it seems like she would be better to be next to the center.
They look at height, don't they?
Tall girls.
There are many small girls in our group,
I am 162cm standing next to someone who is only 145cm,
So when we are in the "eyeshine," it looks as if only one person's head is sticking out.
When I think about it, it is very important to line up in a row.
Mie is about 160cm, and the oldest is 147cm,
Mie and the others would do what we call "link poses," and we would do our link poses here,
If we were lined up like this, our faces would be right here.
They would cover each other.
That's why I did it like this.
That's right. When they are lined up.
The ideal is to have a good balance when you look at them.
As an idol.
Ohno-chan must be tall. If she were like this.
I have an image of Ohno-chan being tall.
I thought so, but then I saw Momona-chan.
Are you placing her next to Momomochi?
Momomomo.
I think Mafui-san looks really slender when I see her in person.
I mean, she's really tiny.
That's why I was wondering if Momochi-san's sprouts
I wonder if the sprouts are good.
I think they are good.
So, Aya...
Ayaka-san...Aya-san, that's not right.
I'm not ashamed of it.
It's just...
I'm just going to make up my own mind.
It's all about balance, isn't it?
As for today...
But it's a matter of consultation.
It may change.
It may change as we talk.
Do you ever do that?
Do you have the timing to be like a royal idol character?
No, not at all.
What kind of character?
First of all, in the group.
I'd like to know.
I don't know.
What character?
Miyu is that one... a rather sharp-tongued one.
What? No, that's a lie!
She's definitely a blabbermouth so far.
She's definitely a blabbermouth.
Really?
The kids in the group are idiots. A lot.
If you ask me, I think they're pretty good.
That's right.
That's why Miya doesn't get involved.
I see.
But there are people who are in charge of organizing and sub-leading the group.
I play the role of the tskkomi, the one who makes the place more relaxed.
It's a clear division. This person is like this.
The ages are quite different.
Younger children are cute. He's a character who can get away with anything.
I think he divides them up pretty well.
I'm surprisingly shy.
I'm quite shy. Right now.
That's right.
I can only joke around with girls in my own group.
Miyoshi's fans who are watching this are nervous.
He's growing up like Mewan.
What about you, MUGI?
I'm a jerk.
No, I'm not. Just once.
I'm pretty much a twintail, not a peon,
I'm the type of person who doesn't really fit in with moe dialogue.
It's the type of life that doesn't really suit moe dialogue or anything like that.
How long have you been playing that character?
Over 10 years, it's too big of a deal, and I can't live without becoming that character.
I'm a veteran.
I'm a veteran. I've been here for 12 years now, so I'm definitely earlier than the others.
When I first joined, I was calling my 20-year-old sisters "aunts,
I thought I had become that one.
You don't wear twin-tail hair anymore?
I only do it when I'm really joking around.
Do you do it when you're joking around?
I only do it when I'm really joking around and I'm going to play this song.
But there may be some fans who are happy to see that kind of gap.
Twintails today?
We wore twin-tails. We did.
Twintails. You're serious. There might be a lot of people who are like that.
That's totally fine.
The type that usually bothers you?
Maybe I forget about it when I get on in the morning.
That's true. I don't really worry about it.
I worry about it at the time, but I solve it quickly.
I envy you.
Worried?
I have a lyric in my introductory song that says, "My worries are endless.
Even if it's a really small thing, I wonder which way it would have been better to go. I get lost.
I want you to solve my problems.
Please tell me how to stay pretty when I'm sweating profusely during a live performance.
Yes! I say.
How much sweat is that?
From about the fourth song, my bangs look like barcodes and my eyebrows disappear.
It's almost like you're taking a bath. It's almost like a bath.
Like after a shower.
I don't really draw my face.
On the contrary, I work really hard, but it's so smooth.
I envy you. I envy the one with the waterfall sweat.
I just wanted to ask you because I've never finished a single one, and I've never finished a single one that was cute from start to finish.
Do you have any countermeasures? Or something.
I'm probably not dealing with it well.I'm probably dealing with it badly.
Why don't you try coping worse?
Hands and sides.
Your hands look like they're in a lot of pain. Mike's going to fly away.
Yeah. So, if there's any pretense of switching mics and holding hands, I'd say, "I'm sorry.
I understand. I understand.
I've seen them hold hands when they say they're sorry because they're sticky with the members.
But not so much with their faces.
Like this.
I'll give it to you.
There are things like, "You should use this kind of cosmetics," or "You should use this kind of cape.
The cape that AKB has always used is a black cape.
It looks a little like a rainbow.
That's right. The one with a rainbow pattern.
That's good.
That's definitely what the makeup artist in the dressing room uses.
They use purple.
Purple really comes off in about two seconds.
There is a black one that is stronger than the purple one.
Is black usually sold in pharmacies?
Yes, they do.
I'm going to go buy some right now.
Maybe that's the one with the strongest bangs.
Next, I would like to ask you about my problem.
I remember their faces, but I can't remember their names.
What should I do in this situation?
That's an issue. This is an eternal issue.
So there are quite a few of these. Quite a few.
And it's a mask.
What?
Who is it? But I've met him before.
And when you come to sign autographs or something, you ask, "Do you remember me? Do you remember me?
Do you remember me? I say yes, yes, yes, but I can't remember their names.
I wonder how they do it.
I'm the type of person who does a lot of ego-searching, so I tell them to check twitter or something.
I'm the type of person who does a lot of ego-searching, so I'd ask them to check out their Twitter feeds, and then I'd go home and I'd remember their characteristics and I wouldn't remember them that day, but I'd look at their tweets and I'd remember them.
I might ask him to show me his twitter. I might tell him that he always sends me replies and I tell him I'm sending them to him.
I'd say, "Oh, I can't find you, so show me your Twitter now," and he'd get curious, and then I'd check in with him and say, "Oh, it's you.
And then they'll be like, "Oh, that's you," and they'll be like, "Oh, you're so good!" That's really helpful.
I don't have much of a technique. If I say, "Do you know your name?
If I say, "Do you know the name of the person?" I'll say, "No, I don't know the name, but I know the face.
I'll say, "Mogi, it's been a long time since you've been here." I'll say, "When was the last time you were here? I'd say, "When was the last time you were here?
I'd say, "Five years ago," and he'd say, "Five years ago." I'd think, "I don't remember that.
So I usually say something like, "There's someone who looks like a classmate of mine..." and she says, "You look like someone close to me.
I give the impression that I remember you because you look like someone close to me, but I think that's a bit too much to ask.
I'm sorry. That was my intention.
But it can't be helped now, can it? It's a mask, after all.
It really gives a different impression.
I haven't seen them in a year or so, so even if it's been a long time, most of them don't remember me.
Maybe with Brazil.
I want to remember. I want to remember.
So the people who come to see me are the most important.
I am happy that they come to see me, and I want to remember them and myself, so I have said many things about how not to hurt them.
I have said many things about how not to hurt them, but I am happy that they come to see me.
That's why I want to remember them.
That's why I do my best.
Miyu, do you have any nicknames that you tend to use? Like fan names?
I don't want to forget.
You never know when you're a hairdresser. When you go out with someone.
So I would have to know his/her hair style, glasses he/she wears, facial features, and so on. Like, "He has permed hair, so he looks like Mr. Broccoli.
Something like that.
I tend to use food as an example.
Doesn't anyone get mad at you for that? Like, "Oh, it's broccoli.
It makes me happy.
What about you, Mogi?
I think of it as a joke, so when I see people who have been using it for almost 10 years, I really feel sorry for them.
I really feel sorry when I see people who have been using it for almost 10 years.
It really doesn't serve any purpose.
If you say "onigiri-kun ne," there are people who will be onigiri-kun for 10 years, so I really feel sorry for those people.
I guess it's important. I guess I was attached to my guesses.
But Kota, Yuta, Sota, and so on.
You know what?
Kota!
Oh, Souta! Like that.
Do you get it?
I totally get it.
I feel like shit at times like that.
But surprisingly, and this may sound rude, but if Yuta and Yuya were together, Yuta would hear me when I say "Yuya".
Probably.
If I say something like, "Thank you, Yuta! If you say it like that.Thank you Yuta! I said something like that.
I think she thought she remembered my name, but then she looked at my Twitter and said, "Oh, like Chada-chan, like Yuta-chan," and I'm sure the next time I see her, she'll be like that.
I don't know if it's a common idol thing, but someone who says it's nice to meet you, but it's the second time you've met.
I wonder why he/she is so shy.
I found the perfect answer to this one.
What?
Am I allowed to say this? Maybe I shouldn't.
If someone says, "This is the second time I've done this," I'll say, "What?
I said, "I thought you were in that kind of shape this time. I can somehow get through.
How nice to meet you this time. So you're just going through the motions? I've studied it over the past 10 years, as if I had thought it was that kind of flirtation.
Whenever someone says, "It's nice to meet you," I always say, "What? Really? I would say, "Really? Many of the patterns are familiar to me.
Surprisingly, when I asked them about it, they said, "How many times have you been to our shows?
How many times have you been to a live concert? There are also people who say it is their first time to talk to me, even though they have seen me perform live before. When I say it's nice to meet you, I ask if it's really the first time.
I check once. But they're cute, too. I'm sure they're digging deep when they ask me "Really?
It's a private conversation. But personally, I think it's good to check.
I'm thinking of doing it when everyone has forgotten about the chekitsui.
I was thinking of doing it when people have forgotten about it.
Best announcer. Thank you!
I'll turn to the last page.
Sweets.
Thank you for the special inside story. As a closing sweet, if these three were in the same group, please take a potential photo for your theme. Thank you very much for coming today.
Latent photo. Potential photo.
If these three people were in the same group. They have a lot in common, don't they?
The color is also blue. Let's try to express blue.
Let's try to express blue. How should I express it?
Blue seems to have a strong image of coolness. No, it's not. No, it's not.
It looks cool. It's a beauty. We have to decide on a potential photo.
Do you have a face to ask? Is it this way?
No, no, no. Maybe it's the other way around.
Then this one is the best. Yes, I'm the most CG.
I'm the most CG. That's the most balanced. I'm all about balance.
Please subscribe to our channel.